Crunched for time, but want a demo? Watch our pre-recorded demo instead!

### Fill out the info below to get the best demo for your business!

Leave this field blank

First Name 

Last Name 

Phone Number 

Email Address 

Company Name 

Potential Users 1-34-1011-4950-99100+

Industry AdjustingCleaningConcreteConstructionConsultingDistribution/SupplyElectricalEngineeringExterminationFlooringHVACInspectionLandscapingManufacturingNot For ProfitPaintingPlumbingPoolsPressure WashingProperty ManagementRemodelingRestorationRoofing/ExteriorsSecuritySign InstallationSolarStoneWindowsOther

Submit

        * 

            Small but mighty.
            
        * 

            Established and growing.
            
        * 

            Industry leaders.
            
        * 

            Using a trusted model.

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

    ### Sign up for a demo.

    * 
        
    * 

        * 

            Document every detail of the job.
            
        * 

            Easily share job site photos.
            
        * 

            Add more context to your photos.
            
        * 

            Discuss everything in one place.
            
        * 

            Organize your photos and projects.
            
        * 

            Scroll through recent updates.
            
        * 

            Collaborate in a digital notebook.
            
        * 

            Connect with your other software.

        * 

            And keep everyone on the same page.
            
        * 

            From anywhere on any device.
            
        * 

            To keep customers and subs in the loop.
            
        * 

            And standardize all your work.
            
        * 

            With a suite of AI actions.

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    NEW
    
    ### Build Pages with AI
    
    AI Tools
    
    Use AI-powered actions to generate shareable overview docs, organized notes, photo reports, summaries, and more.

    * 
        
    * 

        All your burning questions—answered.

        The ins and outs of CompanyCam. 

        We’d love to hear from you. 

    * 

    * 

    ### Contact Support

    * 
        
    * 

            Become a CompanyCam expert.

            Level up your business know-how.

            Learn from industry experts.

            Read industry tips, stories, and news.

            Browse real stories from real customers.

            Choose a workflow based on your role.

            Listen and learn while you work.
            
        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

    ### Savings Calculator

    * 
        
    * 

Menu

[](https://companycam.com/)Menu

        * 

            Small but mighty.
            
        * 

            Established and growing.
            
        * 

            Industry leaders.
            
        * 

            Using a trusted model.

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

    ### Sign up for a demo.

    * 
        
    * 

        * 

            Document every detail of the job.
            
        * 

            Easily share job site photos.
            
        * 

            Add more context to your photos.
            
        * 

            Discuss everything in one place.
            
        * 

            Organize your photos and projects.
            
        * 

            Scroll through recent updates.
            
        * 

            Collaborate in a digital notebook.
            
        * 

            Connect with your other software.

        * 

            And keep everyone on the same page.
            
        * 

            From anywhere on any device.
            
        * 

            To keep customers and subs in the loop.
            
        * 

            And standardize all your work.
            
        * 

            With a suite of AI actions.

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    * 

    NEW
    
    ### Build Pages with AI
    
    AI Tools
    
    Use AI-powered actions to generate shareable overview docs, organized notes, photo reports, summaries, and more.

    * 
        
    * 

        All your burning questions—answered.

        The ins and outs of CompanyCam. 

        We’d love to hear from you. 

    * 

    * 

    ### Contact Support

    * 
        
    * 

            Become a CompanyCam expert.

            Level up your business know-how.

            Learn from industry experts.

            Read industry tips, stories, and news.

            Browse real stories from real customers.

            Choose a workflow based on your role.

            Listen and learn while you work.
            
        * 

        * 

        * 

        * 

    ### Savings Calculator

    * 
        
    * 

### More of a visual learner?

**CompanyCam Privacy Policy**
=============================

_Updated May 6, 2024_

**Your privacy is important to us.**
------------------------------------

We at CompanyCam, Inc. (“we,” ​“us,” or ​“CompanyCam”) respect your privacy, and we don’t ask for information unless we truly need it. We do not collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16 without parental consent. As a data processor, we have limited control over the information provided to us by our users. When you provide data in that sense, you are subject to the Terms of Use. In some limited cases, we may collect information ourselves, but such collection is limited to the information we need to provide you the services.

**The Right to Know**
---------------------

We believe in your right to know what companies are collecting about you and why. This Privacy Policy lays out the details about what we have and what we use it for. Please review it carefully, and if you don’t agree with what we lay out here, please stop using the app and contact us with any questions we can answer.

**Collection of Personal Information**
--------------------------------------

“Personal Information” is information that can be used to identify you as an individual, either alone or taken with other information we collect. Over the course of providing you the services, we may ask for:

* Contact information such as your name, and email address;
    
* Employment information such as your company name, your title, and other company details including address and phone number;
    
* Financial information such as your billing information; and
    
* Location information including your address, IP address, and location data

We collect this information in order to provide our services to you, generally directly from you. We may request the information specifically, or we may collect it through your engagement with certain aspects of our services such as message boards or forums. We do not collect the content of such messages, but we may collect information about the message senders and recipients in order to improve our services. We do not sell or otherwise dispose of your data, though we may transfer it to certain third parties as outlined below.

The lawful basis for our collection of your information is listed below. Where we collect information with your consent (evidenced by your direct provision of the information to us), you can revoke that consent at any time.

* **Contact Information** Necessary in order to perform our contract with you 
    
* **Employment Information** It is in our legitimate business interest to collect information about the types of company using our services. We also use this information to connect individual accounts to their organization and We only collect this information with your consent 
    
* **Financial Information** Necessary in order to perform our contract with you (for billing activities) 
    
* **Location Information** This is automatically collected and used for analytical purposes. Your address is collected in order to perform our contract with you (for billing purposes), and your IP address and location data is anonymized/​not used to personally identify you. 

If you interact with a third party service when using our services, such as if you use Facebook or Google to log-in, or if you share content from our services through a third party service through an integration, we may receive additional Personal Information about you. We only request information as set out above, and we use this information for our legitimate business interest of personalizing the services to improve your experience. We do not purchase or otherwise acquire any Personal Information about you without your knowledge.

### **Data Subjects**

When our customers use the Services, they often input information about their clients (the person whose property they are working on, their ​“**_Clients_**”). We do not use this information for any purpose except to store it and process it on behalf of our customers (we do not use it for our own internal purposes, nor do we sell it in any form). We treat this information as highly confidential and it is entitled to our highest available levels of protection including encryption while on our systems. This information often includes information that would identify the Client individually, such as:

* The Client’s address
    
* The Client’s phone number, email address, or other ways to contact them.
    
* The Client’s name
    
* Photographs of the Client’s property

If you are a Client of one of our customers, you have certain rights related to this data that we have about you. We require that our customers notify you that they will be using CompanyCam, and that they get your consent before sharing your personal information with us. If you feel that your information or photographs of your personal space were uploaded to our app without your consent, please contact us and we will remove them as quickly as possible. Our customers promise that they have your permission to input this information/​upload these photos and that the photos won’t include any personal information about you, but we do not actively monitor uploaded photos to check for personal information included in them. We also require that our customers do not input any personal information belonging to you where it does not belong (outside of a field specifically meant for that piece of information), but we cannot guarantee their compliance with this requirement. If there is a problem, please see the ​“Your Rights to Your Personal Information” section below for more details about your rights in information that is about you.  

### **Collection from Third Party Sources**

We receive information about you from other users, from third party services, and from our business and channel partners.

#### **Other users of the services**

Other users of our services may provide information about you when they submit content through the services. For example, you may be mentioned by someone else on a task, or a team member may upload content about you to CompanyCam. We also receive your email address from other users when they provide it in order to invite you to the services. Similarly, an administrator may provide your contact information when they designate you as another administrator for a task, team or an organizational account.

#### **Other services you link to your account:** 

We receive information about you when you or your administrator enable third-party apps or integrate or link a third-party service with our services. For example, you or your administrator may also integrate our services with other services you use, such as to allow you to access, store, share and edit certain content from a third-party through our services. For example, you may authorize our services to access and display files from a third-party document-sharing service within the services interface. The information we receive when you link or integrate our services with a third-party service depends on the settings, permissions and privacy policy controlled by that third-party service. CompanyCam’s use and transfer of information received from Google APIs to any other app will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements. You should always check the privacy settings and notices in these third-party services to understand what data may be disclosed to us or shared with our services.

#### **Other partners**

We receive information about you and your activities on and off the services from third-party partners, such as advertising and market research partners who provide us with information about your interest in, and engagement with, our services and online advertisements.

#### **Analytics**

Like nearly every website owner out there, we use a variety of analytical tools to make sure that your experience on our website and in our products is as excellent as it can be. Our analytics tools (listed below) generally use cookies to perform their services. You are able to opt-out of cookies at any time, but please be aware that disabling some cookies may cause the services to stop working as intended. To opt-out, you can use the native tools in your browser, or you can use the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

You are encouraged to use the links below to check out the privacy policies of our third party vendors. We do not transfer any information to these vendors, it is collected by their tools when you visit our website and use our services. 

### **Collection of Nonpersonal Information**

Nonpersonal information is information that cannot be used to identify you as an individual, either because it is insufficient to identify you without being combined with other collected data, or because it has been aggregated and anonymized so that it cannot be used to identify you. We collect certain nonpersonal information automatically through the use of cookies and other web beacons to gather information that we can use to improve the services. This may include your browser type, your click information, and other information that we can use for analytics. You can disable cookies and other web services in order to block this automatic collection, but please be advised that such disabling may make the services not work or not work as intended.

**Use of Personal Information**
-------------------------------

We do not sell your personal information. We only use it for our own legitimate business purposes, including certain marketing activities. You are free to object to any such processing at any time by contacting us at the address set out below, but if you choose to do so some of the functions of the services may no longer be available to you. Our uses include:

* providing you with products and services
    
* providing you with information about our products and services
    
* managing and improving our products, services, quality control, administration, communication and internal processes
    
* personalizing and customizing your experience with us
    
* verifying your identity
    
* granting you access to your account with us
    
* investigating any enquiries or complaints submitted by or about you; and/​or
    
* complying with regulatory or legal obligations
    
* To protect us, our business, or our users (e.g. to enforce our terms of service and/​or use, prevent spam, or investigate or protect against fraud)
    
* To maintain the security of our products

We do not share your personal information with third parties, except where required by law, to protect our own rights, or to provide a service to you (see below).

We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary to provide you with a service.

### **Sharing Personal Information**

We will not share your Personal Information with third parties, except where required by law, to protect our own rights, or to provide a service to you. We may, however, disclose anonymized and aggregated versions of this information for business, marketing or public relations purposes. If we share any information, we seek assurances that these contractors agree to (1) protect the privacy of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Privacy Policy and (2) not use or disclose your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing us with the products or services for which we contracted or as required by law. The following are subprocessors that we are currently engaged with and the purpose for which we work with them:

* [Ambition](https://ambition.com/): Sales team software
    
* [AWS](https://aws.amazon.com/): Primary hosting platform
    
* [Calendly](https://calendly.com/): Calendar booking software
    
* [Datadog](https://datadog.com/): Database & server monitoring software
    
* [dbt Labs](https://www.getdbt.com/): Data transformation software
    
* [Drift](http://drift.com/): Marketing software
    
* [Dropbox Sign](https://www.hellosign.com/): Electronic signature application programming interface for executing agreements
    
* [EventBrite](https://www.eventbrite.com/): Event software used for some events
    
* [Fivetran](https://www.fivetran.com/): Data pipeline provider
    
* [Google LLC](https://www.google.com/): Business productivity software
    
* [Helpscout](https://www.helpscout.com/): Customer support software
    
* [Honeybadger](https://honeybadger.io/): Platform performance machine
    
* [Intercom](https://www.intercom.com/): Customer support software
    
* [Jira](https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira): Customer support software
    
* [Kixie](https://www.kixie.com/): Phone and SMS software
    
* [Microsoft](https://www.microsoft.com/): Business productivity software
    
* [Mixpanel](https://mixpanel.com/): Product usage analytics software
    
* [MongoDB](https://mongodb.com/): Cross-platform database
    
* [Salesforce](https://www.salesforce.com/): Customer Relationship Management software (CRM)
    
* [Slack](https://slack.com/): Internal communication software
    
* [Snowflake](https://www.snowflake.com/): Data warehouse
    
* [Stripe](https://stripe.com/): Payments processor
    
* [SurveyMonkey](https://www.surveymonkey.com/): Customer feedback software
    
* [Vitally](https://www.vitally.io/): Tracks customer health and communication
    
* [WorkOS](https://workos.com/?utm_source=stackoverflow&utm_medium=blog&utm_campaign=sept2022): Authentication platform
    
* [Zoom](https://zoom.us/): Video call software that we use for demos and webinars

We may also share your Personal Information with law enforcement if we believe we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, or other lawful order by a court or law enforcement. We may disclose Personal Information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use, to detect fraud, or to protect the safety and/​or security of our users, the CompanyCam services or the general public.

We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

### **Feedback**

From time to time, you may be asked to provide Feedback (as such term is defined in the Terms of Use) related to the Services. Provision of Feedback is optional. If you choose to provide Feedback, we may use your Feedback in the form of a written testimonial posted online. Absent your permission, we will not attribute such Feedback directly to you, but we may attribute it generally to you (“Sally from Lincoln, NE”). We will not use any personally-identifiable information in such feedback without your permission, which we may request via email or other communication with you.

### **Cookies**

We use ​“cookies” to collect information about you and your activity across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit so we can understand how you use our site and serve you content based on preferences you have specified.

If you do not wish to accept cookies from us, you should instruct your browser to refuse cookies from our website, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired service without them. This policy covers only the use of cookies between your computer and our website; it does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### **Types of cookies and how we use them**

##### **Essential cookies**

Essential cookies are crucial to your experience of a website, enabling core features like user logins, account management, shopping carts and payment processing. We use essential cookies to enable certain functions on our website.

##### **Performance cookies**

Performance cookies are used in the tracking of how you use a website during your visit, without collecting personal information about you. Typically, this information is anonymous and aggregated with information tracked across all site users, to help companies understand visitor usage patterns, identify and diagnose problems or errors their users may encounter, and make better strategic decisions in improving their audience’s overall website experience. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. We use performance cookies on our site.

##### **Functionality cookies**

Functionality cookies are used in collecting information about your device and any settings you may configure on the website you’re visiting (like language and time-zone settings). With this information, websites can provide you with customized, enhanced or optimized content and services. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party service. We use functionality cookies for selected features on our site.

##### **Targeting/​advertising cookies**

Targeting/​advertising cookies are used in determining what promotional content is more relevant and appropriate to you and your interests. Websites may use them to deliver targeted advertising or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. This helps companies improve the effectiveness of their campaigns and the quality of content presented to you. These cookies may be set by the website you’re visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. Targeting/​advertising cookies set by third-parties may be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. We use targeting/​advertising cookies on our site.

##### **Third-party cookies on our site**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals on our websites — for example, analytics providers and content partners. We grant these third parties access to selected information to perform specific tasks on our behalf. They may also set third-party cookies in order to deliver the services they are providing. Third-party cookies can be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. As we have no control over third-party cookies, they are not covered by our cookie policy.  
  
The above excludes text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

**Your Rights to Your Personal Information**
--------------------------------------------

We believe in your personal rights to your Personal Information. Therefore, we honor and recognize the following rights that you have over such information:

### **The right to know –** 

This Privacy Policy is here to disclose to you what we have and what we use it for. If you have any questions about the data we have, you can always ask. 

### **The right to opt-out of the sale of your data –** 

We do not sell your data at any time, so there’s no need for you to opt out.

### **The right to be forgotten –** 

You can request that we delete all or some of your data from our systems. 

### **The right to withdraw consent –** 

If we are processing your Personal Information based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that if you exercise this right, you may have to then provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Information, if such use or disclosure is necessary to enable you to utilize some or all of our services. 

### **The right to object –** 

You can contact us to let us know that you object to the further use or disclosure of your Personal Information for certain purposes, such as for direct marketing purposes.

### **The right to restrict processing –** 

You can ask us to restrict further processing of your Personal Information

### **The right to correct –** 

You can request that we correct any Personal Information we hold about you that may be incorrect or incomplete

### **The right to access –** 

You can request more information about the information we have about you and can request a copy of that data by contacting us at the contact information set out below.

If you live in the EU, you also have the right to file a complaint about our data practices with the supervisory authority in your country or EU member state. 

### **California Privacy Rights**

CompanyCam complies with the California Consumer Privacy Act (referred to in this Privacy Policy as ​“CCPA”) as set forth by the State of California. If the CCPA applies to your personal information this Privacy Policy provides you with information regarding how to receive information about our privacy practices, as well as request access to, and deletion of your personal information.

California consumers may make a request pursuant to their rights under the CCPA by contacting us using the contact information below. Upon receiving a request, we will verify your request using the information associated with the services, including your email address. Government identification may be required. Consumer can also designate an authorized agent to exercise these rights on the consumer’s behalf.

**Business Transfers**
----------------------

If we or our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, we would include user information among our assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any parties who acquire us may continue to use your personal information according to this policy.

**Security**
------------

We take security seriously and do what we can within commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information from loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data.

**Links to Other Sites**
------------------------

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot assume responsibility for their treatment of your personal information. This privacy policy only covers our website and privacy practices.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**
---------------------------------

At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be reflected here, so we encourage you to visit this page regularly. We will also notify our registered users of updates to our policy. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information.

**Contact Us**
--------------

350 Canopy Street, Suite 230, Lincoln, NE 68508. 

hello@​companycam.​com

Our Data Protection Officer is Chad Wilken, and he can be reached at the above email address.

Sign up for a free account.
---------------------------

Get your team up and running in less than 3 minutes.

 Get Started Today

_No credit card required_ _Available on iOS, Android, and Web_

CompanyCam helps contractors build trust with their crews and customers through photo documentation. We make it easy to keep everyone on the same page with an actively growing list of features and integrations.

##### Product

##### Learn

##### About

* ©2024 CompanyCam  |  [Terms of Use](https://companycam.com/terms)  |  [Privacy Policy](https://companycam.com/privacy-policy)
